http://www.coloradocyclist.com/pages/privacy

BikesMountainRoadCyclocross & GravelElectric BikesWheelsMountainRoadRoad DiscTires, Tubes & AccessoriesComponentsComponentsGroupsetsLevelsDrivetrain, BrakesForks, Cockpit, PedalsMenTopsBottomsShoes & PedalsAccessoriesWomenTopsBottomsShoes & PedalsAccessoriesMaintenanceToolsStandsPumpsLubricants & CleanersAccessoriesApparelElectronicsTrainers, RollersFood, NutritionHydration SystemsStorage, TravelHealth & RecoveryMiscellaneousClearanceMy AccountContact UsMon-Fri 9am-5pm MSTPricingReturnsShipping Shopping CartCheckoutEdit CartSubtotal$0.00×COLORADO CYCLISTMost Orders Over $100 Ship Free * Contact Login/Register Cart (0)BikesMountainJulianaSanta CruzRoadColnagoBianchiRoad Bike SaleCyclocross & GravelSanta CruzJulianaElectric BikesSanta Cruz E-BikesBianchi E-BikesWheelsMountainFactory / Pre-Built WheelsCustom Hand-Built MTB WheelsRoadFactory WheelsCustom Hand-Built Road WheelsRoad DiscFactory WheelsCustom Hand-Built WheelsTires, Tubes & AccessoriesTiresTubesAccessoriesSaleComponentsRimsHubsSkewersSpokesNipplesComponentsGroupsetsRoad/Gravel Bike GroupsetsMountain Bike GroupsetsLevelsCampagnolo Super RecordCampagnolo RecordCampagnolo ChorusCampagnolo EkarShimano Dura AceShimano UltegraShimano GRX 800Shimano 105 7000Shimano XTR Shimano XTShimano SLXSram RedSram ForceSram XXSram XOSram GX EagleSram NX EagleDrivetrain, BrakesBottom BracketsBrakesCablesCassettes & CogsChains & Chain GuidesCranksets & ChainringsDerailleursDrivetrain Small PartsElectronic ComponentsPowermetersShiftersForks, Cockpit, PedalsForksGripsHandlebarsHandlebar TapeHeadsetsPedals & CleatsSaddlesSeatpostsSeatpost ClampsStemsMenTopsJacketsJerseysVestsBase LayersBottomsShorts & BibsTights & KnickersShoes & PedalsMen's Mountain ShoesMen's Road ShoesReplacement PartsPedals & CleatsAccessoriesGlovesBody ArmorHelmetsHats & HeadbandsShoe CoversSocksSunglassesWarmersWomenTopsJacketsBottomsShorts & BibsShoes & PedalsMountainRoadReplacement PartsPedals & CleatsAccessoriesGlovesBody ArmorHelmetsHats & HeadbandsShoe CoversWarmersMaintenanceToolsWheel BuildingCassetteChainCrank, Bottom BracketHeadsetMulti-Tools, Hex KeysTool KitsOtherStandsBike WorkstandsWheel Truing StandsWorkstand AccessoriesPumpsFloorFrameCO2 InflatorsPartsShockLubricants & CleanersLubricantsCleanersAccessoriesApparelBody ArmorGlovesHelmetsHats & HeadbandsShoesShoe CoversSocksSunglassesWarmersElectronicsComputersGPS, Data RecordersComputer, Heart Rate Monitor PartsLighting SystemsPowermetersTrainers, RollersTrainersRollersPartsFood, NutritionVitamins/SupplementsHydration SystemsHydration Packs & BagsWater BottlesCagesWater ReservoirsStorage, TravelCar RacksCar Rack AccessoriesStorageTravel CasesHealth & RecoveryEmbrocations & CreamsMiscellaneousBooks, MapsFenders, Frame ProtectionLocks, BellsBicycle Saddle BagsGift CertificatesClearancePrivacy PolicyThank you for visiting ColoradoCyclist.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using ColoradoCyclist.com, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not a retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit this site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.Note:The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for ColoradoCyclist.com only. If you encounter links to external web sites from within our site, please review the relevant privacy policies posted at those sites for their specific uses.Information We CollectWe only collect personally identifiable information when voluntarily submitted by you, our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information will only be used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add your information to our mailing list. Any additional information that is gathered is used to help us personalize and improve your experience at ColoradoCyclist.com. Here are the forms of information we gather.Information You Provide:We receive and store any information you enter on our web site, along with other forms of communication. You can choose not to provide certain information, though this may prevent you from being able to complete the process where you are entering this data. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests and orders, customizing your shopping experience, communicating with you, and improving our web site.Automatic Information:We receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit ColoradoCyclist.com. Like many online retailers, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when you visit ColoradoCyclist.com. The technical data that we gather is: your IP address, login information, e-mail address, password, computer and connection information (such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform), the URL clickstream to, thru, and from our Web site, including date and time, cookie number, and products you viewed or searched for. We only gather the email address and password supplied by you to log in. We do not gather other email addresses or passwords from your computer. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.E-mail Communications:If you elect to receive email messages from ColoradoCyclist.com, your email address will be added to our mailing list. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, you may opt out at any time by clicking a link in the bottom of the email message, or by visiting ColoradoCylist.com and clicking the "unsubscribe" button under "Email List".What Are "Cookies"?Cookies are random number-letter identifiers that are placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit ColoradoCyclist.com. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser, manage your login and allow storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. You can configure your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being placed. Refer to the Help tab in your browser to learn how to change these settings. ColoradoCyclist.com requires cookies to be enabled, or allowed, to provide you with the full range of services that we offer.What Information Gets Shared?ColoradoCyclist.com does not share or sell any personally identifying information gathered from our visitors with any agency or company for marketing purposes. We may share this information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when permitted or required by law, while trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or while investigating fraud which has already taken place.Is My Information Safe?Any personally identifiable information we may acquire from our visitors will be kept in a secure manner. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to likewise keep information secure and confidential according to our privacy policies) of ColoradoCyclist.com have access to this information.Transmission of your order is protected by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts your information.It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.Questions?We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:The Colorado Cyclist, Inc.3970 E. Bijou St.Colorado Springs, CO 80909USAYou may contact us by e-mail at support@coloradocyclist.com, or call us at 800-688-8600.Our Favorite BrandsTop quality and performanceSanta CruzDevinciShimanoCastelliSidiNewsletterSpecial offers & updates in your inboxAccountOrdersPasswordPoliciesPricingShippingReturnsLinksBike Fit GuideBrandsCareersContact Us800-688-8600support@coloradocyclist.comMon-Fri 9am-5pm MSTView Address      DiscoverVisaAmerican ExpressMaster CardPayPal© 2020 The Colorado Cyclist IncPrivacy PolicyTerms of Service
